jonloomer.com 2018-11-27

# Refund Policy, Terms of Service and Privacy Policy - Jon Loomer Digital

  Jon Loomer Digital, LLC (“Jon Loomer Digital“) operates JonLoomer.com and may operate other websites.

Jon Loomer Digital is committed to protecting the privacy of visitors to our website, subscribers to our newsletters, webinar registrants, PHC members, training program members, and those providing contact information. In addition, Jon Loomer Digital is opposed to unauthorized commercial e-mail delivery, otherwise known as spam.

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy and Spam Policy, or to report spam abuse, please send an e-mail to [info@jonloomer.com](mailto:info@jonloomer.com). It is Jon Loomer Digital’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites.

### HOW YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION MAY BE USED

Jon Loomer Digital collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Jon Loomer Digital’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Jon Loomer Digital’s visitors use its website. From time to time, Jon Loomer Digital may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

Jon Loomer Digital also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on JonLoomer.com blogs/sites. Jon Loomer Digital only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below, except that commenter IP addresses and email addresses are visible and disclosed to the administrators of the blog/site where the comment was left.

Jon Loomer Digital may use your personal information in the following ways:

  * To operate and maintain the website;
  * To create your account, identify you as a user of the website, and customize the website to your account;
  * To send you promotional information, such as newsletters. Each e-mail newsletter will provide information on how to opt-out of future mailings by unsubscribing;
  * To send you administrative communications, such as administrative e-mails, confirmation e-mails, technical notices, updates on policies, or security alerts;
  * To respond to your comments or inquiries;
  * To provide you with user support;
  * To track and measure website performance;
  * To process payment for purchases you make through Jon Loomer Digital;
  * To protect, investigate, and deter against unauthorized or illegal activity;
  * To review the effectiveness of our marketing programs and analyze other general demographic trends;
  * To notify you of new information or services that may be of interest to you; or,
  * To send promotional materials.

Jon Loomer Digital does not rent or sell your personally identifiable information with third-parties. We may, however, share your information with third-parties when we are authorized to share such information.

 **Third-party service providers**  
Jon Loomer Digital may use third-party service providers to service various aspects of the website. Each third-party service provider’s use of your personal information is dictated by their respective privacy policy.

 **Opt in:** Jon Loomer Digital Uses Opt In Monster for opt in options. Opt In Monster: [Privacy Policy](https://optinmonster.com/privacy/).

 **Social Sharing:** Mashshare is used in order to make content, such as blog posts on JonLoomer.com shareable with other social networks. Mashshare: [Privacy Policy](https://mashshare.net/privacy/).

 **Tracking:** Jon Loomer Digital uses various marketing tools that help us create a better user experience for people visiting our site. These tools allow us to look at aggregated data such as scrolling patterns, clicks, and allow us to run tests to determine which pages result in the best actions. However, your personally identifiable information is not used by any of these tools. We use the following third-party service providers for tracking: Google Analytics: [Privacy Policy](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245?hl=en).

 **Remarketing:** Jon Loomer Digital uses remarketing tracking cookies and conversion pixels from vendors such as Google and Facebook to present special offers to you for our products or services over the Google Content Network and via social networks. This means you may see an ad for one of our products or services as a result of visiting our website. In addition, Jon Loomer Digital uses custom audiences based on e-mails of subscribers and customers. This allows us to present special offers for our products and services to you via Facebook. However, your personally identifiable information is not used by any remarketing service other than to present you special offers from us. We use the following third-party service providers for remarketing:

 **Twitter:** [Privacy Policy here](https://help.twitter.com/en/safety-and-security#ads-and-data-privacy)  
**Facebook:** [Opt-out of Facebook remarketing here ](https://www.facebook.com/help/568137493302217)  
**Google:** [Opt-out of Google remarketing here](https://support.google.com/ads/answer/2662922?hl=en)

 **Contact Information and Website Support:** We offer multiple ways to contact Jon Loomer Digital including contact forms, e-mails, and chat. If at any time, you attempt to contact us through a contact form, the information you provide will be stored on our servers. If you use the chatbot feature, it will be stored on the servers of Chatfuel. You may view Chatfuel’s [privacy policy here](https://chatfuel.com/PrivacyPolicy.pdf). Facebook Chat Widget: [Privacy Policy](https://www.facebook.com/business/m/messenger-and-the-gdpr).

 **Comments:** Jon Loomer Digital uses Disqus to make it easy for you to leave comments on blog posts. Personal information that you enter for comments will be stored on the Disqus servers, in accordance with the Disqus [Privacy Policy](https://help.disqus.com/terms-and-policies/disqus-privacy-policy).

 **Newsletters:** Jon Loomer Digital uses Infusionsoft as its e-mail service provider. Infusionsoft collects contact information, distributes our newsletter, and tracks actions you take that assist us in measuring the performance of the website and newsletters. You may view Infusionsoft’s [privacy policy here](https://www.infusionsoft.com/legal/privacy-policy). At any time, you may be removed from our newsletter list by clicking on the unsubscribe button provided in each e-mail.

 **Purchases:** Jon Loomer Digital uses Stripe to service payments for most purchases of services and memberships. Stripe collects personal information such as your name, e-mail address, address, and payment information. You may view Stripe’s privacy [Privacy Policy](https://stripe.com/ca/privacy).

Jon Loomer also uses PayPal. This service stores your name, amount of your purchase, and payment details on their site. You may view PayPal’s privacy [Privacy Policy](https://www.paypal.com/ca/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full).

Upon making a purchase, you will receive e-mail confirmations to the e-mail address you provide during your purchase.

Webinars: Jon Loomer digital host webinars, which are hosted through Zoom or GoToWebinar. If you elect to participate in a webinar, you will be required to submit personal information to register and login. You may also receive e-mail communications regarding reminders and playback availability.

To view GoToWebinar’s privacy policy, please [click here](https://www.logmeininc.com/legal/privacy).  
To view Zoom’s privacy policy, please [click here](https://zoom.us/privacy).

### Website Visitors

Jon Loomer Digital collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Jon Loomer Digital’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Jon Loomer Digital’s visitors use its website. From time to time, Jon Loomer Digital may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by sharing results from a Jon Loomer Digital Facebook marketing campaign.  
Jon Loomer Digital also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on JonLoomer.com blogs/sites.

Jon Loomer Digital only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below, except that commenter IP addresses and email addresses are visible and disclosed to the administrators of the blog/site where the comment was left.

 **Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information**  
Certain visitors to Jon Loomer Digital’s websites choose to interact with Jon Loomer Digital in ways that require Jon Loomer Digital to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Jon Loomer Digital gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up at JonLoomer.com to provide a username and email address.

Those who engage in transactions with Jon Loomer Digital are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, Jon Loomer Digital collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with Jon Loomer Digital. Jon Loomer Digital does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

 **Aggregated Statistics**  
Jon Loomer Digital may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. Jon Loomer Digital may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Jon Loomer Digital does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

 **Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information**  
Jon Loomer Digital discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Jon Loomer Digital’s behalf or to provide services available at Jon Loomer Digital’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Jon Loomer Digital’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them.

Jon Loomer Digital will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Jon Loomer Digital discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when Jon Loomer Digital believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Jon Loomer Digital, third parties or the public at large.

If you are a registered user of a Jon Loomer Digital website and have supplied your email address, Jon Loomer Digital may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Jon Loomer Digital and our products or services. If you send us a request (for example via email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Jon Loomer Digital takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Jon Loomer Digital uses cookies to help Jon Loomer Digital identify and track visitors, their usage of Jon Loomer Digital website, and their website access preferences. Jon Loomer Digital visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Jon Loomer Digital’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of Jon Loomer Digital’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

 **Business Transfers**  
If Jon Loomer Digital, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Jon Loomer Digital goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Jon Loomer Digital may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

### RIGHTS RELATED TO YOUR PERSONAL DATA

 **Opt-out:** You may opt-out of future e-mail communications by following the unsubscribe links in our e-mails. You may also notify us at [info@jonloomer.com](mailto:info@jonloomer.com) to be removed from our mailing list.  
**Access:** You may access the personal information we have about you by submitting a request to [info@jonloomer.com](mailto:info@jonloomer.com)  
**Amend:** You may contact us at [info@jonloomer.com](mailto:info@jonloomer.com) to amend or update your personal information.  
**Forget:** In certain situations, you may request that we erase or forget your personal data. To do so, please submit a request to [info@jonloomer.com](mailto:info@jonloomer.com).  
Please note that we may need to retain certain information for recordkeeping purposes or to complete transactions, or when required by law.

### CHILDREN’S INFORMATION

Jon Loomer Digital does not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 16. If a parent or guardian believes that Jon Loomer Digital has personally identifiable information of a child under the age of 16 in its database, please contact us immediately at [info@jonloomer.com](mailto:info@jonloomer.com) and we will use our best efforts to promptly remove such information from our records.

### SPAM POLICY

Jon Loomer Digital is strongly opposed to spam. We will only send e-mail to users that have explicitly requested to receive an e-mail from Jon Loomer Digital. Examples may include:

  * Opt-in subscribers to the Jon Loomer Digital Newsletter
  * Users that complete a contact form
  * All communication will be related and relevant to what you have requested.

### WEB LINKS

Occasionally, Jon Loomer Digital contains links to other sites. Please be aware that Jon Loomer Digital is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site to read the privacy and spam policies of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This Privacy and Spam Policy applies solely to information collected by Jon Loomer Digital.

### Terms and Conditions

 **Self-serve Courses:**  
Digital, self-serve courses are available for purchase on this website. If, for any reason, you are not satisfied with your purchase, you may request a refund within 15 days.

When requesting a refund you must provide the email that you used to purchase the course, and you may be required to provide proof of purchase depending on your payment method.

 **One on One Sessions:**  
Note that time slots are at a premium and are often booked days or weeks in advance. If you reschedule, you are essentially taking two time slots. If you cancel, that spot is often not fillable at the last minute.

As a result, appointments cannot be rescheduled, and cancellations will not be refunded. If a new time is needed, payment will be required for that second meeting time as well.

 **Power Hitters Club (PHC):**  
Annual memberships to PHC are not eligible for any refunds due to the fact we provide such deep discounts on the annual pricing.

Cancellation requests for month to month PHC members must be made 10 days before your billing date. We cannot refund month to month fees unless we are notified within 24 hours of the charges to your account.

All refund requests must be sent through the support tab to the left or via [info@jonloomer.com](mailto:info@jonloomer.com)

### HOW DO I CONTACT JON LOOMER DIGITAL?

If you have any further questions or comments regarding the Jon Loomer Digital website or this Privacy and Spam Policy, you may contact [info@jonloomer.com](mailto:info@jonloomer.com).
